## **YEN HUNG LIN**

----

hello@yenhunglin.com yenhunglin.com

#### SKILLS

#### **Computer Programs Shop Skills** Sketch Band saw Invision Bridgeport mill Zeplin Drill press Laser cutter After Effects Miter saw Painting Photoshop Sanding Illustrator Vacuum forming InDesign

## Keyshot Scripting Languages

HTML CSS JS

Mandarin Chinese Taiwanese

Languages

#### Other

Package model making ID Sketching

#### SELECTED RECOMMENDATIONS

## Heidi Bullock // Chief Marketing Officer at Tealium

I feel very fortunate to have worked with Jeff. He is incredibly talented and can take a high level marketing concept and breath life into it. Jeff is also a unique talent because he is outstanding at UX as well, so companies can have a cohesive feel across external marketing and product. Jeff is thoughtful and responds well to feedback. He is someone I would hire again!

# **Grant Grigoriany //** Director of Product Management at Engagio

Jeff is an absolute pleasure to work with. We worked together closely on the product team and were able to iterate on many visual designs within a very short period of time: which led to more customer validation, more feature variations, more ideas, and a better product in the end. This rapid paced iteration and ideation would not be possible without Jeff on the team.

I highly recommend Jeff, and would love an opportunity to work with him in the future.

#### SELECTED EXPERIENCES

#### Engagio // San Mateo, CA

2018-Present, Visual, UI Designer

Working with PM, UX designers, engineers, and the marketing team to define the visual and the interactive elements of the user interface for our products; keeping our team's UI library organized and up-to-date; and brand design projects.

#### MOCACARE // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan

2017-2018, UI/UX, Visual Designer

Working with the industrial design team and the product design team to locate user needs and to explore various solutions. Projects included MOCACARE hardware, packaging, and app.

### HTC // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan

2014-2015, Visual, Package Designer

Working with the industrial and packaging team on packaging, animation, UI, and graphic design. Also accompanied designers to factories, met with vendors for study of new materials, and built a good work relationship with vendors.

#### San Francisco Art Institute // SF, CA

2014, Graphic Design Intern

In charge of weekly event poster designs, gallery show invitation designs, school publications, and school event photo documentation.

#### CCA Sputnik Design Studio // SF, CA

2013, Graphic Designer

In charge of Phase Forward: First Year Exhibition 2013, CCA 2013 Annual Fashion Show, Upstart: CCA Commencement Events 2013, CCA Fashion Design Promotion Fall 2013, and CCA President's Letter Fall 2013.

## **EDUCATION**

## California College of the Arts

2013, BFA in Graphic Design